export default data11 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Which of the following is a Crown Dependency but not part of the UK?",
        options: ["Shetland", "Isle of Wight", "Isle of Man", "Anglesey"],
        correct_option: "Isle of Man"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Is the BBC controlled by the government?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        correct_option: "No"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "How many members does the Northern Ireland Assembly have?",
        options: ["12", "60", "90", "110"],
        correct_option: "90"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Who was in charge of the British fleet at the Battle of Trafalgar?",
        options: ["Oliver Cromwell", "The Duke of Wellington", "Robert the Bruce", "Admiral Nelson"],
        correct_option: "Admiral Nelson"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "What was inscribed in the first coins to be minted in Britain during the Iron Age?",
        options: ["The names of Iron Age kings", "The names of Iron Age Gods", "The names of trees", "The names of animals"],
        correct_option: "The names of Iron Age kings"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Towns, cities and rural areas in the UK are governed by government appointed officials.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Where is the Tate Art Gallery located?",
        options: ["Glasgow", "Cardiff", "London", "Belfast"],
        correct_option: "London"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "The version of the Bible created by King James I is known as:",
        options: ["Authorised version", "Reformed version", "Approved version", "Unique version"],
        correct_option: "Authorised version"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "What is the period of the 1960s known for?",
        options: ["A downgrade in manufacturing", "A growth in British fashion and pop music", "A shortage of water", "A blockage of social laws"],
        correct_option: "A growth in British fashion and pop music"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "Between 1680 and 1720 many refugees called Huguenots came to England, which country did they come from?",
        options: ["Pakistan", "Germany", "India", "France"],
        correct_option: "France"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "What is the most famous tennis tournament played in the UK?",
        options: ["The Queen's Club Championships", "Wimbledon", "Roland Garros", "The Aegon Championships"],
        correct_option: "Wimbledon"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "MPs can only be contacted at their office in the House of Commons.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "What is the day when jokes are published in newspapers and telecasted on TV?",
        options: ["April Fool’s Day", "Boxing Day", "Halloween", "Valentine’s Day"],
        correct_option: "April Fool’s Day"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Which Scottish king defeated the English at the Battle of Bannockburn?",
        options: ["King Charles I", "King James I", "Admiral Nelson", "Robert the Bruce"],
        correct_option: "Robert the Bruce"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Who invented the World Wide Web?",
        options: ["Sir Tim Berners-Lee", "Sir Peter Mansfield", "Sir Ian Wilmot", "Sir Robert Edwards"],
        correct_option: "Sir Tim Berners-Lee"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "You have to be at least 21 years old to serve on a jury.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "Which of the following major sports event took place in the UK in 2012?",
        options: ["The Football World Cup", "The Rugby World Cup", "The Olympic games", "The Eurocup Basketball"],
        correct_option: "The Olympic games"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Charles I believed in the ‘Divine Right of Kings’ so he tried:",
        options: ["To rule without the Parliament", "To rule with the approval of the Parliament", "To raise money for the Parliament", "To restore Catholicism in Britain"],
        correct_option: "To rule without the Parliament"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "What is the Union Jack?",
        options: ["The Flag of the Commonwealth", "The Flag of the United Kingdom", "The shield used by British Knights", "A trade union to protect workers rights"],
        correct_option: "The Flag of the United Kingdom"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "Who was voted the greatest Briton of all time in 2002?",
        options: ["Mo Farah", "Admiral Nelson", "Winston Churchill", "Clement Attlee"],
        correct_option: "Winston Churchill"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "British values and principles are based on history and traditions and are protected by law, customs and expectations.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a devolved administration?",
        options: ["The Scottish Parliament", "The Welsh Assembly", "The Irish Parliament", "The Northern Ireland Assembly"],
        correct_option: "The Irish Parliament"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Who built a wall in the north of England to keep out the Picts (ancestors of the Scottish people)?",
        options: ["Emperor Claudius", "Napoleon", "Emperor Hadrien", "Julius Caesar"],
        correct_option: "Emperor Hadrien"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Who looks after Edinburgh Castle?",
        options: ["Historic Scotland", "SEPA", "The Scottish Parliament", "The National Trust"],
        correct_option: "Historic Scotland"
    },
    
]